mydailyflog.com 2013-11-26

# Welcome to MyDailyFlog! | MyDailyFlog

This Privacy Policy applies to your use of the MyDailyFlog website at MyDailyFlog.com. The website is owned by Refriendz Ltd (UK)

At MyDailyFlog your privacy is of paramount importance. As the custodians of your personal information, we have developed this policy to ensure that your privacy is always protected while you are using the MyDailyFlog network.

By accessing or using the website, you agree to our Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to these terms, please do not access or use this site.

## What Does This Privacy Policy Cover?

This Privacy Policy covers MyDailyFlog's treatment of personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") that you submit or that may be gathered when you use the MyDailyFlog web site. The types of Personal Information collected include information such as, your name, email address and geographical information.

## How Does the Privacy Policy Apply to Children?

We understand that young people need special safeguards and privacy protection. We realize that they may not understand all the provisions of our Privacy Policy or be able to make thoughtful decisions about the choices that are made available to our adult users. We strongly urge all parents to participate in their children's exploration of the Internet and any online services, and to teach their children about protecting their personal information while online. This site is not directed to children under the age of 13. Please refer to the MyDailyFlog Terms of Use for more information regarding permitted uses of the web site.

## What Personal Information Does MyDailyFlog Collect?

The information we gather enables us to personalize and improve our services and respond to customer service requests. We collect the following types of information.

## Personal Information You Provide to Us

  * We may receive and store any information or content you enter on the MyDailyFlog site when you register for an account, fill out your profile or participate in any of our community services.
  * The Personal Information you provide may be used for such purposes as providing the MyDailyFlog products and services, customizing the content you see, responding to customer service requests, research, billing, communicating with you about marketing efforts, support and maintenance issues and new products.

## Personal Information Collected Automatically

  * We may automatically receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with our web site or services. 
  * MyDailyFlog may choose to automatically receive and record information on our server logs that come as a standard part of typical web browser page requests including your IP address, browser type and version, and the page you requested.
  * We may also automatically collect usage information, such as the numbers and frequency of visitors to our site and its different areas and components.
  * MyDailyFlog generally only uses this data in aggregate form as a statistical measure, and not in a manner that would identify you personally. As part of this use of information, we may provide aggregate information to our partners about how visitors, collectively, use our site.
  * If your browser accepts cookies, MyDailyFlog may automatically collect individualized information regarding your visits to MyDailyFlog's site ("Individual Usage Information") to provide you with a more personalized experience. If you do not wish to have your Individual Usage Information collected, please see the "More About Cookies" section below for further information.

## More About Cookies

Many Websites, including MyDailyFlog, use cookies. Cookies are small files of data that we may transfer to your computer's hard drive through your browser.

  * These cookies enable our systems to recognize your browser and tell us how and when pages in our site are visited and by how many people.
  * These cookies also enable us to recognize you as an individual when you visit the MyDailyFlog site so that we can personalize your site experience and provide access for you to your individual account information and functionality.
  * If you do not wish to have your Individual Site Usage Information or Personal Information you provide to us stored, most browsers have an option for turning off the cookie feature, which will prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, as well as (depending on the sophistication of your browser software) allowing you to decide on acceptance of each new cookie in a variety of ways. If you do not accept cookies from MyDailyFlog you may not be able to access key pieces of member functionality
  * In some cases, our business partners may use cookies on our site. For example, an advertiser like Google may place a cookie on your computer to keep track of what country you are from so they show ads in the correct language. MyDailyFlog has no access to or control over these cookies.
  * We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and would like to know your options in relation to·not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.co.uk/privacy_ads.html).

## Can I update or Change the Personal Information that MyDailyFlog has Collected?

Members can access, review, and edit their registration and profile information on our site by visiting the [Settings](http://www.mydailyflog.com/go/settings/account_info) page.

## Will MyDailyFlog Share Any of the Personal Information it Receives?

We neither rent nor sell your individually identifiable Personal Information to anyone. We share your Personal Information only with your consent or in the following scenarios:

Business Partners and Agents:

We may employ or work with other companies and people and therefore we may need to share your information with them to provide products and services to you. We will inform you if your information will be shared with such parties.

Business Transfers:

If MyDailyFlog, or substantially all of its assets, are acquired by another company, member information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of MyDailyFlog may continue to use your Personal Information as set forth in this Privacy Policy. We will inform the MyDailyFlog member base with a conspicuously posted notice on the site if this occurs.

Protection of MyDailyFlog and Others:

We may release Personal Information when we believe in good faith that release is necessary to comply with any law; enforce or apply our terms of use and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of MyDailyFlog, our employees, our members, or others.

## Is My Personal Information Secure if I Link to Other Web Sites?

The MyDailyFlog web contains links to sites operated by third parties that are not under the control or supervision of MyDailyFlog. Neither MyDailyFlog nor its employees, agents or representatives are responsible for the privacy practices of these sites. These sites may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies, or no policies at all. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of the other sites to see how your personal information will be handled on the third party sites before providing them with your personal information.

## Effective Date of this Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is effective as of August 1, 2008.

## Changes to this Privacy Policy

MyDailyFlog may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time. Use of information we collect now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time such information is collected. If we make changes in the way we use Personal Information, we will notify you by posting an announcement on our web site.

## Questions or Concerns

All rights including trademarks, copyright and database rights in this site are owned by or licensed to MyDailyFlog which is owned and operated by Refriendz Ltd.
